Guide to the Peter H.L. and Edith Chang Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Manuscripts
  - Subseries 2.3: Manuscripts by Others on H. L. Chang
    - Kwangdong Army Hundred and Third Anniversary Select Memorial Committee Preface of Nine Salutes to Peter H. L. Chang, [Taipei] June, 1990, (8 page printed pamphlet ) (Box 12, Folder 01)
    - Wang Zhuo-ran What Kind of A Person Is Peter H. L. Chang, Peiping [n.d.], (40 leaf ms (bond) and printed pamphlet (33 pages) with same title ) (Box 12, Folder 01.01)
    - Edith Chao Chang What Kind of A Person Is Peter H. L. Chang, Taiwan [1990], (3 page, autograph manuscript (photocopy, 25 copies) ) (Box 12, Folder 01.02)
      [See: Manuscript [Box 11 Folder 03]]
    - Raymond Moore China Doctor, New York [n.d.], (75 page, typed manuscript (galley proof) ) (Box 12, Folder 02)
    - Shigeo Nishimura On Peter H. L. Chang’s Three Year Reign, Shenyang 1994, (10 page (photocopy) ) (Box 12, Folder 03.01)
    - Shigeo Nishimura On Peter H. L. Chang’s Visit to Europe, Taiwan 8/1997, (49 page (photocopy) ) (Box 12, Folder 03.02)
    - Immanuel C. Y. Hsu The Rise of Modern China, London 1970, (102 page, printed document(photocopy) ) (Box 12, Folder 03.03)
    - Branow, Steven A. To Edith Chang, Seattle, June 26, 1995, (1 page letter ) (Box 12, Folder 03.03)
    - Shigeo Nishimura On Peter H. L. Chang’s Visit to Europe, Taiwan 12/12/1996, (36 page, printed document(photocopy) ) (Box 12, Folder 04.01)
      [Note: All the items in Folder number 4 are printed essay bound pamphlets containing copies of papers presented at the Sixtieth Anniversary Xian Incident Research Conference held in Taipei on December 22, 1996.]
    - Zhu Wen-yuan The Soong Brother and Sister and Xi An Incident, Taiwan 12/12/1996, (70 page, printed document ) (Box 12, Folder 04.02)
    - Chen Cun-gong The Military Campaign in Western Shanxi by the Red Army Prior to the Xi An Incident, Taiwan 12/12/1996, (48 page, printed document with I page printed campaign map ) (Box 12, Folder 04.03)
    - Liu Wei-kai A Study of Shan Cheng Bao Battle, Taiwan 12/12/1996, (34 page, printed document with1 page printed campaign map ) (Box 12, Folder 04.04)
    - Su Deng-ji On Chiang Kai-shek’s Visit to Xi An, Taiwan 12/12/1996, (25 page, printed document ) (Box 12, Folder 04.05)
    - Wang Ke-wen On Wang Jing-wei before and after Xi An Incident, Taiwan 12/12/1996, (38 page, printed document ) (Box 12, Folder 04.06)
    - Xu Yu-ming The Reaction of the Japanese Public Opinion during the Xi An Incident, Taiwan 12/12/1996, (28 page, printed document ) (Box 12, Folder 04.07)
    - Xu Nai-li The Changes in the Relationship between Central and Regional Governments during the Xi An Incident and before the breakout of Anti-Japanese War, Taiwan 12/12/1996, (16 page, printed document ) (Box 12, Folder 04.08)
    - Yang Wei-zhen Long Yun, Liu Xiang and the Xi An Incident, Taiwan 12/12/1996, (29 page, printed document ) (Box 12, Folder 04.09)
    - Zhang Li Historical Data Relevant to Lan Zhou Incident---Textual verification and Discovery, Taiwan 12/12/1996, (22 page, printed document ) (Box 12, Folder 04.10)
    - Agenda of the Seminar on Xi An Incident, Convened at its 60th Anniversary, Taiwan [12/12/1996] 1 p p.d. (Box 12, Folder 04.11)
    - Liu Ming- Jiu Support Unity, Loyalty to the Nation, [Beijing?] 12/4/1996, (9 page, typed manuscript ) (Box 12, Folder 05.01)
    - Liu Ming-jiu Address to the Sixtieth Anniversary Conference on the Xian Incident, [Beijing?] 12/10/1996, (6 page, typed manuscript ) (Box 12, Folder 05.01)
    - Tang De-Gang On the Fiftieth Anniversary of the Xian Incident, [Taipei] 1986?, (5 and a half page article (photocopy from Literary and Recordings Journal: Volume 50, No. 2, pages 26-31) ) (Box 12, Folder 05.02)
    - Wu Tian-wei The Xian Incident and the Great Turn In Modern Chinese History, [Taipei] 1986-7?, (7 and a half page article (photocopy from Literary Studies and Recordings Journals Volume 50, No. 2, pages 31-38) ) (Box 12, Folder 05.02)
    - Wang Yu-ren The Xian Incident: A Terrible Disaster (Part 1), [Taipei] 1986-7?, (8 page printed article (photocopy from Literary and Recordings Journal: Volume 51, No. 2, pages 47-54) ) (Box 12, Folder 05.02)
    - Wang Yu-ren The Xian Incident: A Terrible Disaster (Part 2), [Taipei] 1986-7?, (9 page article (photocopy from Literary and Recordings Journal: Volume 51, No 3, pp.107-115) ) (Box 12, Folder 05.02)
  - Subseries 2.4: Manuscripts by Others on Chang Tso-lin
    - [?] Memorial Album, [Fengtian] [n.d.], (15 leaf manuscript (29 pages), and 60 page (31 leaf photocopy of album) ) (Box 12, Folder 06.01)
    - Hollington Tong Draft of "My Father" (Chang Tso-lin), [n.p.] 30/6/1965, (44 page typed manuscript and 1 page typed letter ) (Box 12, Folder 07.01)
    - Hollington Tong Preliminary Notes and Draft of "My Father" (Chang Tso-lin), [Taipei] October 17, 1960 and January 13, 1961, (41 page typed manuscript ) (Box 12, Folder 07.02)
    - Cai Zheng-lian The Assassination of Chang Tso-lin, [Taipei] 10/11/m35 [1946], (67 page book ) (Box 12, Folder 08)
  - Subseries 2.5: Miscellaneous Notes
    - One address book with 11 pages of handwritten notes (Box 41, Folder 04)
    - One notebook with 64 pages of handwritten notes (Box 41, Folder 04)
    - Two handwritten pages of book lists (Box 41, Folder 04.01)
    - One notebook with 14 handwritten pages of notes (Box 41, Folder 04.02)
    - One handwritten page of notes (Box 41, Folder 04.03)
    - One notebook with nine handwritten pages of notes (Box 41, Folder 04.04)
- Series III: Documents
  - The Pacific Command of Gansu Province To [Peter H. L. Chang], [n.p., n.d.], (4 page, manuscript document (copy) ) (Box 06, Folder 04)
    [The letter is a List of Military Personnel with Titles and Commanding Regions]
  - [Unknown] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 leaf, manuscript document ) (Box 06, Folder 13)
    [The content of the letter is two alternative plans for military assignment after Xi An Incident]
  - Unknown Sender: Notice of retirement funds To Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei; n.d., (2 page, autograph letter ) (Box 33, Folder 01.01)
  - H. L. Chang Materials Relating to KMT membership reform, [n. p.] 4/10/1949, (18 sheets (36 pages) handwritten ) (Box 33, Folder 03)
    [18 page p.d.]
  - Retirement Order, [n.p.] April, 1946, (1 sheet ) (Box 33, Folder 01.01)
  - Edith Chang Republic of China Passports, Taipei: February 17, 1967, May 20, 1976 and June 9, 1982, (33, 33 and 26 page respectively ) (Box 33, Folder 01.02)
  - Edith Chang Exit Visa, Taipei: October 20, 1989, (8 page booklet ) (Box 33, Folder 01.03)
  - Peter H. L. Chang Hospital Receipt, Taipei: October 26, 1979, (1 page ) (Box 33, Folder 02.01)
  - Certificates of Appointment of Peter H. L. Chang as Honorary President of Northeastern University, Shenyang, China: March 8, 1993, (2 copies-each in ornamental boxes ) (Box 33)
  - Yan Yu Heng Educational Foundation Scholarship Acknowledgement Certificate, [n.p.], June, 1991, (1 sheet ) (Box 33)
  - Du Ze Shu Book Research Academy Honorary Director Appointment Certificate, [n.p], September 25, 1992, (1 sheet ) (Box 33)
  - Harbin Industrial University Honorary President Appointment Certificate, Harbin, China: April 18, 1993, (1 sheet ) (Box 33)
  - Shenda Academy Honorary Director Appointment Certificate, [n.p.] August 8, 1993, (1 sheet ) (Box 33)
  - Name cards of Zhang Xueliang, [n.p., n.d.] (Box 34, Folder 01.13)
  - Medical Reports of Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei: June 10, 1952; December 5, 1957; January 13, 1966; May 20, 1971 and November 9-13, 1972, (18, 20 and 27 pages respectively for second, fourth and fifth respectively- first and third have no pagination ) (Box 34, Folder 01.02)
  - Mausoleum Diagrams and Correspondence, Honolulu, 1994-1996, (4 plans and 16 correspondence items including 3 fax photocopies ) (Box 34, Folder 03)
    [4 plans and 16 correspondence items including 3 fax photocopies]
  - 18 Architectural Plans and 7 Correspondence items, Yang Mingshan, Taiwan: [v.d. ] 1960 (Box 34, Folder 04)
    [18 plans and 7 correspondence items]
  - Miscellaneous Lists and Publications (on flowers), Taipei: [n.d.], (3 items of 8, 8 and7 printed pages respectively-the last with 1 page of handwritten notes and 1 item of 3 single( 5 double ) loose pages ) (Box 34, Folder 02.01)
  - Chang, Peter H. L. Materials Relating to Peter H. L. Chang's 95th. Birthday Celebration, Taipei: March 28-June 1, 1995, (2 pages typed schedule; 2 pages typed Thanksgiving and Testimony; 2 pages typed songs; one page handwritten menu; 2 page seating plan. ) (Box 33, Folder 05)
  - Manuscripts and other Materials on Raising Orchids, Taipei, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 02.02)
    [Six manuscripts of 10, 25, 16, 30 ,14 and 15 p. respectively]
  - Minzu Wanbao, Taipei? February 26, [year unclear], (1 page ) (Box 34, Folder 02.02)
  - Minzu Wanbao, Taipei: March 19, 1969, (1 page ) (Box 34, Folder 02.03)
  - Celebratory Pamphlet of Flower Exhibition in Honor of Peter H. L. Chang's 98th. Birthday, Shenyang, China: May 7-12, 1998, (4 pages ) (Box 34, Folder 02.03)
  - International Orchid Exchange Institute In Honor of Peter H. L. Chang 98th. Birthday Flower Exhibition, Shenyang; May, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 02)
    [96 page celebratory book of Photos and other materials]
  - Alumni Association of China's Northeastern University, China-U.S. Chapter, Silver Spring, Maryland: [v.d.] 1990-1994, (One handwritten note and one page with printed attachment, April 23, 1993; two one-page printed notices, April 17,1993 and April 22, 1993 ) (Box 35, Folder 01.01)
  - Lian Hebao, Taipei; April 17, 1993, (1 page (photocopy) ) (Box 35, Folder 01.01)
  - 1 page (photocopy- on same page as above Lian Hebao article) China Times, Taipei: April 5, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 01.01)
  - Northeast Normal University, Changchun, Jilin, China: May 25, 1990, (2 page, autograph letters ) (Box 35, Folder 01.02)
  - Northeastern University, Shenyang, Chima: October 18, 1993 and April, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 01.03)
    [1 page printed note and1 page printed photocopy respectively]
  - Name cards of He Jicheng and Wang Qiyi-President and Vice-President respectively of Northeastern University (Box 35, Folder 01.04)
  - Newsletter of the Alumni Association of China Northeastern University: USA Chapter, No: 1, Silver Spring, Maryland?: November, 1993, (37 pages ) (Box 35, Folder 01.05)
  - Professor Lee Hung Peng To Edith Chang, Honolulu: February 9,1994 (Box 35, Folder 01.06)
    [1 page a. l. s.,1 page photocopy of photos wth notes on back, and 1 sheet calligraphy.]
  - Ministry of Education Documents, Taipei: December, 1960, January, 1991 and [n.d.], (1 page Registration Form for Yang De Chun ) (Box 35, Folder 01.10)
    [1 page Registration Form,1 page Tax List and 2 p handwritten title pages.]
  - United Nations Command, Korea; The UNCREG (Repatriation Group). Story: Munsan-Ni Korea, September 1,-December 31, 1953., Honolulu: January, 1954?, (19 page pamphlet ) (Box 35, Folder 01.11)
  - Northeastern University of Technology Friendship Association, Taipei: November 15, 1975, (35 page pamphlet photocopy and two fax cover sheets from the Northeastern University of technology) (Box 35, Folder 01.12)
  - Northeastern University Introductory Pamphlet, Shenyang: October, 1993, (14 pages ) (Box 35, Folder 02)
  - Northeastern University Memorial Library Plans and Photos, Shenyang: April, 1994, (35 pages ) (Box 35, Folder 02)
  - Northeastern University introductory Pamphlet, Shenyang: August, 1995, (72 pages ) (Box 35, Folder 02)
  - List of Books Donated by H. L. Chang to Tunghai University, [n. p.] March 26, 1993, (70 pages ) (Box 35, Folder 03)
  - Plan Of Chang Reading Room at Columbia Rare Book Library, New York: May 18, 1995, (1 sheet ) (Box 35, Folder 04.01)
  - Peter H. L. Chang's remarks on arrangements for donating his materials to and opening of a reading room for him at Columbia's Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York: October 21, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 04.03)
    [Two 3 page copies and 2 2 page and 1 3 page photocopy and one separate sheet of a. handwritten notes]
  - Collection of Classical Literature, [n.p., n.d.], (106 page bound volume manuscript ) (Box 36, Folder 01)
  - Joyful Poem, [n.p., n.d.], (1 long sheet (8 folded p.) handwritten manuscript ) (Box 36, Folder 01)
  - Dedication Gift Plaques to Edith Chang from Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei: [v.d.]1962-1963, (5 individual plaques ) (Box 36, Folder 02)
  - Birthday Gift Plaque to his wife Edith, Taipei?: 1985, (1 plaque ) (Box 36, Folder 03)
  - Dedicatory Gift Plaques from H. L. Chan, Taipei: 1985 [n.d] and January 28, 1995, (2 plaques ) (Box 36, Folder 04)
  - Calligraphic Plaque About a White Haired Friend by Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] January 28, 1995, (1 plaque ) (Box 36, Folder 05)
  - Calligraphic Plaque of the Book of Yi Chuang by Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] October 21st, 1996, (1 plaque ) (Box 36, Folder 06)
  - Calligraphic Plaque of article by Peter H. L. Chang on the Xian Incident, [n.p., n.d.], (1 plaque (photocopy of page 12) ) (Box 36, Folder 07)
  - Pamphlet of a Chiang kai-shek Sheep Pasturage, Taipei: January 1, 1973, (8 pages ) (Box 37)
  - Forms and Photos of the Orchid Exhibition in Honor of Peter H. L. Chang's 98th. Birthday, Shenyang; March 5 and May 2-6, 1998, (2 copies of 1 sheet invitation forms and 1 sheet (4p.) photos ) (Box 37, Folder 01.01)
  - Wenhui bao, Shanghai: March 8, 1998, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 37, Folder 01.01)
  - Xingdao Ribao, Hong-Kong? June 8, 1997, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 37, Folder 01.02)
  - Photocopy of 22 page handwritten list of seals with photos of the seals belonging to Peter Chang (Box 41, Folder 06.01)
- Series IV: Study Notes
  - Subseries IV.1: Peter Chang
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Certificate and Diploma for Bible Studies from the following correspondence bible schools: Sheng-Ming-Zhi-Guang (1963),Yuan Dong-Gui-Zhu(1964),Pu-Shi-Jia-Yin(1970), The Seminary External Education Division (SEED) (1983-84), [v.p.] 1963 - 1984, (13 page, printed document, and copy of catalogue of Seminary Extension Department of Southern Baptist Convention School in Nashville, Tennessee ) (Box 13, Folder 01.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Course work: Pu Shi Jia Yin Correspondence School, [Taipei] [1960], (20 page printed document and 11 bound printed volumes of course work of 45, 42, 9, 8, 7, 9, 8, 10, 10, 11, and 11 pages respectively ) (Box 13, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Course work: Yuan Dong Gui Zhu Correspondence School, [Taipei] 25 February.1963 - 14 May 1964, (16 page registration materials. and ten printed volumes of course work and exercise materials of 46, 82, 24, 36, 28, 22, 24, 20, 42, and 15 pages respectively ) (Box 13, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Course work: The Seminary Extension Department, Southern Baptist Convention [SEED], [Taipei] 1965, (59 page bound printed volume, 61 page exercise book with interspersed handwritten pages, 1 page manuscript and 1 bound 58 page manuscript ) (Box 13, Folder 04)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 1966, (57 page bound volume study aid with 6page manuscript and 85 page with notes, study aids and exams, and a second 78 page bound volume study aid, with 11page manuscript, 60 page study aids, exams and notes and a 44p manuscript ) (Box 13, Folder 05)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Course work: SEED, [Taipei]]1967, (77 page autograph manuscript and printed. pages ) (Box 13, Folder 06)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 1968, (95 page bound volume and 63 page typed and handwritten manuscript ) (Box 13, Folder 07)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 1969, (80 page bound volume; 58 page typed and handwritten manuscript; 107 page bound volume; 69 page typed and handwritten manuscript ) (Box 13, Folder 08)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 1970, (2 copies of three different bound volume textbooks of 82, 24, and 28 pages respectively, with handwritten notes and 3 page work sheets and 1 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 13, Folder 09)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Course Introduction: SEED, [Taipei] [v.d.], (13 pages of course information and 2 page manuscript notes ) (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Certificate from Far Eastern Sacred Study School, Taipei: June 12, 1963, (1 page ) (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Certificate From Overseas Crusades Bible Investigation Correspondence School, Taipei: March 26, 1965, (1 page ) (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Certificates of Study Completion From The Seminary Extension of Southern Baptist Ministries, Nashville, Tennessee: September 26, 1978, (1 page ) (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Test Sheet: SEED?, Taipei: [n.d.], (1 typed pages ) (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 1980-1981, (69 page bound volume study guide and 41 page work sheets ) (Box 14, Folder 01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 1987-1988, (2 copies 65 page (bd.) volume study guides and 10 page study notes and exams ) (Box 14, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Course work: SEED, [Taipei] [1988], (84 page bound volume study aid, 2 page printed test and 1 page handwritten manuscript ) (Box 14, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Tests: SEED, [Taipei] 3 December 1970-11 October 1989, (50 page printed study notes with comments and handwritten notes ) (Box 14, Folder 04)
    - Chinese reading materials, [n.p., n.d.], (27, 29, and 187 printed pages and separate 4 printed pages ) (Box 14, Folder 05)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Documents: Academic, Course and Financial matters (SEED), [Taipei] 17 February 1968 -20 March 1989, (25 page financial forms and 51 printed and typed pages, including correspondence regarding academic matters ) (Box 14, Folder 06.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: Gospel Parallels, [Taipei] [n.d.], (12 page typed manuscript, with handwritten notes ) (Box 14, Folder 07.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: Gospel Parallels, [Taipei] [n.d.], (52 page ms pages with handwritten notes ) (Box 14, Folder 07.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes and Questions: Gospel Parallels, [Taipei] [n.d.], (82 page manuscript notes, one 17 page and one 37 page manuscript in bound notebooks and 6 page pages of Christian pamphlet or book ) (Box 14, Folder 07.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: Gospel John, [Taipei] [n.d.], (35 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 14, Folder 08.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: Old Testament, [Taipei] [n.d.], (Two bound 21 and 43 page manuscripts and 39 loose pages manuscript ) (Box 14, Folder 09)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: Gospel Mark, [Taipei] 23/4/1963, (40 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 14, Folder 10.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: Gospel Mark, [Taipei] [n.d.], (Two spiral notebooks of 31 page and 28 page manuscript notes ) (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: Gospel Mathew, [Taipei] [n.d.], (17 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 14, Folder 11.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: Evaluation Test, [n.p., n.d.], (1 typed page ) (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: Textual Verification, [Taipei] [n.d.], (26 study aid cards autograph manuscript ) (Box 15, Folder 01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: Vocabulary, etc., [Taipei] [n.d.], (3 tiny notebook s of 7, 25, and 4 page manuscript respectively. ) (Box 15, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Research into Information on the United States, [n.p., n.d.], (Five Volumes of 54 sheets (105p.), 48 sheets (96p.)-part 1- 46 sheets (92p.)-part 2, 64 sheets (127p.), 63 sheets (124p.) and 37 sheets (73p.) respectively plus 17 pages in English entitled: "The United States and World Relations," in Volume 5 ) (Box 15, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Notes on Various World War II Statesman, Politicians, Military Officers and Events, [n.p., n.d.], (136 sheets (231 page not including blank name sheets) ) (Box 15, Folder 04)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Three Principles of the People, [n.p., n.d.], (7 page handwritten exercise book ) (Box 15, Folder 05)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Seminary Extension of Southern Baptist Seminaries, Nashville, Tennessee [v.d.], (10 study completion certificates ) (Box 15, Folder 06)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Cards: Study Notes (Philosophy), [n.p., n.d.], (autograph manuscript ) (Box 16)
      [In 2 wooden boxes and a copy of the Bible in Chinese]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Book of Psalms in Chinese, Hong Kong, 1962, (109 page pp volume ) (Box 16, Folder 01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: History, [n.p., n.d.], (40 page autograph manuscript ) (Box 16, Folder 02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: English, [n.p., n.d.], (4 notebooks of 5, 14, 37 and 56 page manuscript Respectively ) (Box 16, Folder 03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. Study Notes: English, [n.p., n.d.], (14 page vocabulary word (unbound notebook) ) (Box 16, Folder 04)
    - Reference Lists, New York: March, 2002, (20 typed pages ) (Box 37, Folder 04.01)
    - Reference Notes, New York? [n.d], (8 page pad and 3 loose sheets with handwritten notes ) (Box 37, Folder 04.01)
    - Reference Name Lists and Temporary Cross Reference Notes, New York: 2002 (Box 37, Folder 02.01)
      [31 page and 21 page respectively]
    - Miscellaneous notes, [n.p., n.d.] one dated 17th. day, (2 manuscripts of one page each ) (Box 37, Folder 03.01)
    - List of Books, [n.p., n.d.], (1 typed page ) (Box 37, Folder 03.05)
    - Notes, [n.p., n.d.] 1 double-sided page handwritten notes (Box 37, Folder 03.05)
  - Subseries IV.2: Edith Chang
    - Edith C. Chang Course work: Correspondence Bible School of Taiwan, [Taipei] 1965, (41 page pages some with study notes ) (Box 17, Folder 01)
    - Edith C. Chang Course work: Emmaus Bible School, [Taipei] 1965, (32 page typed 12 lessons with handwritten exercises and a registration certificate ) (Box 17, Folder 02)
    - Edith C. Chang Course work: Various Bible Correspondence Schools, [Taipei] 1964, (2 page notepad; 16 page notebook, 3 bd. ) (Box 17, Folder 03)
      [Study aid volumes of 23, 44 and 15 printed pages respectively and 113 loose printed pages of study aids, some with handwritten notes ]
    - Edith C. Chang Course work: Presbyterian Bible School, [Taipei] 1964, (38 page bd. Volume of "The Gospel according to St. Matthew," (published in England) [n.d.], 4 bound workbook volumes of 20, 22, 24 and 28 pages printed pages with some handwritten notes respectively, 2 printed pamphlets of 4 and 6 page respectively and two paper receipts. ) (Box 17, Folder 04)
    - Edith C. Chang Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 1965 -1966, (1 page letter to Edith from Ralph Herring from Nashville on April 6 1966, one 59 page bound volume workbook and 208 loose pages of printed and typed pages, with some of printed pages with handwritten notes. ) (Box 17, Folder 05)
    - Edith C. Chang Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 1966, (78 page bound volume study guide, 90 page typed manuscript and 9 pages handwritten manuscript ) (Box 17, Folder 06)
    - Edith C. Chang Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 8/1/1966, (Three paper notebooks of 7, 30 and 20 pages respectively ) (Box 17, Folder 06.01)
    - Edith C. Chang Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 1967, (78 page bound volume study guide, 86 page handwritten manuscript and 88 page printed study aid and typed manuscript ) (Box 17, Folder 07)
    - Edith C. Chang Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 1967 -1968, (95 page bound volume study aid and 67 page study aid ) (Box 17, Folder 08)
    - Edith C. Chang Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 1969, (Two bound study guides of 107 and 80 page respectively and 88 and 52 pages of study notes respectively in each ) (Box 18, Folder 01)
    - Edith C. Chang Course work: SEED, [Taipei] 1970, (Two bound study guides of 22 and 82 page respectively and 1 pages notes. ) (Box 18, Folder 02)